usadvl.org 2010-06-12

# Green Card Lottery, Apply and win the USA Green Card Lottery, USADVL, Live & work in America

Click Here to Register Online !  
WINNERS will get free Air Line Ticket to USA*

## PRIVACY POLICY AND STATEMENT OF USADVL.org

Legal Statement And Acceptable Use Policy Of [http://www.usadvl.org](http://www.usadvl.org/) and all related sites owned, operated or controlled by "USADVL Organization"

**Information Collection and Use**  
_USADVL Organization_ is the sole owner of all the information collected on this site. _USADVL Organization_ will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. _USADVL Organization_ collects information from our users at several different points on _USADVL Organization_ website. Personal email addresses are obtained to ease points of communication between clients and the USADVL Organization. 

**Order**  
_USADVL Organization_ request information from the user on order form. Here a user must provide contact and personal information (such as, but not limited to, name and address) and financial information (such as, but not limited to, credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If _USADVL Organization_ has trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. _USADVL Organization_ uses the user's information for other purposes as well. 

**Use of Cookies**  
_USADVL Organization_ uses cookies to gather and store information. Cookies are pieces of data that a web site transfers to user computer's hard drive solely for record-keeping purposes. Cookies help _USADVL Organization_ make its software more useful by storing information on your preferences. There is nothing unusual about the use of cookies by a web site and they are an industry standard. They do not personally identify you, but they will identify your computer. Your browser is most likely set up to accept cookies, but you can set yours to refuse them. If you do so, you may not be able to take full advantage of _USADVL Organization_ 's web site. _USADVL Organization_ is not liable for any failure of your computer due to the use of cookies. 

**Log Files**  
_USADVL Organization_ use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
_USADVL Organization_ share aggregated demographic information with partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. _USADVL Organization_ use an outside shipping company and a credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. _USADVL Organization_ partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, _USADVL Organization_ will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that _USADVL Organization_ is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. _USADVL Organization_ encourages users to be aware when they leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by _USADVL Organization_ Web site. 

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time _USADVL Organization_ site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Emails**  
All emails sent to users adhere to the strict requirements of the CAN-SPAM Act. Email addresses are only obtained by a customer freely giving their email address from client's own free will ("Affirmative Consent"). This registration process is understood by the USADVL Organization as a request for additional information about the service. Once a client has paid for the service, emails are sent to aid in the process of registration, by verifying that information has been correctly entered, photos have been successfully uploaded, and to update the client upon his registration status. Each time an email is sent, users have the ability to opt-out of the email subscription, by either clicking the 'unsubscribe' link provided at the bottom of each email, or by sending an email, fax or telephone request to the USADVL Organization. 

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use _USADVL Organization_ referral service for informing a friend about this site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. _USADVL Organization_ will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. . After the first email sent, additional emails will only be sent to the friend, if he chooses to register to the USADVL site of his own accord. The friend may contact _USADVL Organization_ at any time to request the removal of the information from the database. 

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and off-line. When registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as the payment reply form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked. 

This is the official USADVL Organization web site, which specializes in the registration to the American Green Card Lottery program for clients all over the world. When registering with the USADVL Organization, users should take precaution that they do not register with any site that pretends to be the USADVL Organization. To verify that a registration is with the USADVL Organization, users should check that at the top of the browser it is written USADVL. 

**Special Offers**  
_USADVL Organization_ send all new clients who registered on the site a welcoming email with information and invitation to register for the service.  
_USADVL Organization_ send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users _USADVL Organization_ present the option to not receive these types of communications.  
_USADVL Organization_ may send clients who registered on the site Special Offers of third parties. USADVL Organization may transfer the client's information to a third party for receiving Special Offers and/ or Commercial E-mails as long as the third party guarantees to protect and respect the CAN-SPAM Act. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires _USADVL Organization_ service, _USADVL Organization_ will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to _USADVL Organization_. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing _USADVL Organization_ Customer Support. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
USADVL Organization users have the ability to opt-out of receiving emails from the USADVL Organization. An opt-out request may be sent by email, telephone or fax, or by clicking the link provided at the bottom of each email sent to users. Should a user choose to opt-out of the email subscription, the USADVL Organization will honor the request and will not send additional emails. 

Version 10.3 - Last updated August 2007
